<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YMCA Website Services Docs on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in YMCA Website Services Docs on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Designs</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/layout-builder/designs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/layout-builder/designs/</guid><description>The distribution has shipped with two versions of Layout Builder component designs. The first-generation &amp;ldquo;Pre-release&amp;rdquo; designs were shipped with version 9.2.12 (December 2022) and 9.2.13 (March 2023). The revised and feature-complete &amp;ldquo;Design System&amp;rdquo; designs shipped with the June 2023 release.
Design System Discover our Design System in our interactive UI kit.
Colorways Based on the YMCA Brand Guide, the distribution contains four &amp;ldquo;colorways&amp;rdquo; that allow content editors to apply accessible, brand-compliant styles to all components on a Layout Builder-based page.</description></item><item><title>August 13, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/08/13/august-13-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/08/13/august-13-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Shelley Goetz and Avi Schwab from the Core team and Michael DeTorre, Joe Michaelson, and Jeff Greer from VMLY&amp;amp;R to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s coming up in the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Services roadmap.
Agenda items include:
Release Schedule Reminder An explanation of the Small Y Template project Font Licensing - for Cachet and Montserrat fonts Product Roadmap Reminder Community Call Time Change - Now on the 2nd Wednesday of each month at 11am CT Virtual Y - Sunset Reminder Recording Resources Slides - August 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.3.3</title><link>/blog/2024/08/13/digital-services-release-10.3.3.3/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/08/13/digital-services-release-10.3.3.3/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Updates Continuing general cleanup, updated documentation, and improvements to the content editing experience for new Layout Builder components and content types.
Learn more in our docs.
WYSIWYG / Simple Content - Created the ability for Y admins / content editors to copy text from Word and paste it into the WYSIWYG, and have the WYSIWYG clear out text formatting from Word. (#1308) Social Sharing - Updated the y_lb share block to replace the Twitter logo with the X logo.</description></item><item><title>July 9, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/07/09/july-9-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/07/09/july-9-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Shelley Goetz and Avi Schwab from the Core team to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s coming up in the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Services roadmap.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release Schedule Changes Description of the Small Y Template Security Updates Virtual Y - sunsetting at end of 2024 Recording Resources Slides - July 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.3</title><link>/blog/2024/06/12/digital-services-release-10.3.3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/06/12/digital-services-release-10.3.3/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Drupal Updates Learn more about the improvements in Drupal 10.1 and Drupal 10.2.
For users who wish to apply all the updates below without Drupal 10.2, we&amp;rsquo;ve released YMCA Website Services 10.3.2.4. This can be applied as a stepping stone to Drupal 10.2, but we recommend moving to 10.2 as community security support for Drupal 10.0 ended in December 2023.
Updated to Drupal core version 10.2. (#758) NOTE: This release will work with Drupal 10.</description></item><item><title>June 11, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/06/11/june-11-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/06/11/june-11-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Stasya Paliienko, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to demonstrate features in the June release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release timeline updates Showcasing new Activity Finder updates Layout Builder improvements: Scheduling Options, Updated Schema, and Meta Tags Canadian Colorway Improvements Virtual Y - sunsetting at end of 2024 Recording Resources Slides - June 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>May 7, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/05/07/may-7-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/05/07/may-7-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Avi Schwab and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to demonstrate features in the forthcoming June release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release timeline updates Showcasing new Activity Finder updates A closer look at Website Service&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation Design System The &amp;ldquo;dark mode&amp;rdquo; enhancements and why they are important. Recording Resources Slides - May 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>April 8, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/04/08/april-8-2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/04/08/april-8-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, and Roman Salo from the Core team to demonstrate newly released features from the March point release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release timeline updates Demo of updates to Weekly Schedule Management An in-depth description of the website update process from YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Hosting Service and YMCA partners Recording Resources Slides - April 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.2.1</title><link>/blog/2024/03/28/digital-services-release-10.3.2.1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/28/digital-services-release-10.3.2.1/</guid><description>Bug Fixes [Promotion Content Type] Admins can view a preview of promotion items before publishing. (#1333) [Layout Builder] Fixed the button fill of the CTA button in the Program Categories listing view block. (#1334) [Menus] Fixed issue with menu links with long text not wrapping on mobile devices. (#1337) [Layout Builder] Made dropdown icons in the Article/Events filters clickable. (#1352) Fixed broken Header in Lily theme. (#1353) [Layout Builder] Fixed stretched body field inside Layout Builder components.</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.2</title><link>/blog/2024/03/12/digital-services-release-10.3.2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/12/digital-services-release-10.3.2/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Updates Continuing general cleanup, updated documentation, and improvements to the content editing experience for new Layout Builder components and content types.
Learn more in our docs.
Layout Builder - Program CT - Added styling for &amp;ldquo;Categories listing&amp;rdquo; view block to match the new styles for headers, buttons, etc. (#1273) Layout Builder - Simple Content / WYSIWYG - Included approved brand headers colors into the default color selector.</description></item><item><title>March 12, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/03/12/march-12-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/12/march-12-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Roman Salo, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to demonstrate newly released features from the March release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Demo of Weekly Schedule Management Explanation of the Polyfill issue fix Description of the Text Editor fix for creating buttons Events entry and display improvements, now with recurring options! Traction Rec Integration Update Recording Resources Slides - March 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.9.0</title><link>/blog/2024/03/12/virtual-y-1.9.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/12/virtual-y-1.9.0/</guid><description>Updates Upgraded Axios library for Virtual Y. (#889) Polyfill Security update. (#1357)</description></item><item><title>Polyfill Security Notice</title><link>/blog/2024/02/29/polyfill-security-notice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/02/29/polyfill-security-notice/</guid><description>Summary YMCA Website Services relies on some external code to provide broad browser support to JavaScript applications (like Virtual Y, Activity Finder, and Group Schedules). One of those codebases recently changed owners, which resulted in sporadic failures.
Users can incorporate the use Fastly polyfill patch for the openy_custom module as soon as possible to mitigate the issue.
What is the problem? Polyfill is a service that makes web development less frustrating by selectively polyfilling just what the browser needs.</description></item><item><title>February 9, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/02/09/february-9-2024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/02/09/february-9-2024/</guid><description>Sandeep Goswami and Tom Gardner are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap, including an update about the TractionRec/Y-CRM, upcoming security updates, and addressing community questions.
Recording Resources Slides - February 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>January 9, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/01/09/january-9-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/01/09/january-9-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap.
Recording Due to a technical issue there is no meeting recording available.
Resources Slides - January 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>December 12, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/12/12/december-12-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/12/12/december-12-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap, including a demonstration the new Promotion content type and the Program &amp;amp; Subprogram content types in Layout Builder.
Recording Resources Slides - December 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.1.1</title><link>/blog/2023/12/12/digital-services-release-10.3.1.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/12/12/digital-services-release-10.3.1.1/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Promotion Content Type Promotions are pieces of content with scheduled start and end dates that can be used for displaying internal marketing and ad campaigns. Content editors can easily schedule, manage and place multiple promotions throughout their website via the Drupal admin interface.
The first version of this content type allows content editors to place promotions inside the Card component (for Layout Builder) and as interstitial content within Activity Finder.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.8.18</title><link>/blog/2023/12/12/virtual-y-1.8.18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/12/12/virtual-y-1.8.18/</guid><description>Bug Fixes Fixed an issue with YV Logs using the old instructor name field. (#903) Fixed the Header (utility menu and main nav) so that it does not overlap the content below. (#1076) Fixed the empty description on Live Stream/Virtual Meeting causing the page to fail. (#1240) Credit: Sathya Raja</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.0.1</title><link>/blog/2023/11/14/digital-services-release-10.3.0.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/11/14/digital-services-release-10.3.0.1/</guid><description>Sandbox Demo Content Pages Home page Who We Are (About) Programs Overview Programs Category (i.e. Youth Sports) Individual Program (i.e. Soccer) Membership Join Donate Location Finder Location page (i.e. YMCA Springfield) Schedules Events Individual Event Contact Us Jobs Volunteer Opportunities Documentation Updates Drupal 10 update assistance. (#787) Documentation for Layout Builder Facility Content Type. (#1034) Documentation for Layout Builder Icon Grid component. (#1041) Documentation for Alerts. (#1035) Added instructions for adding/restoring the Camp Header block state.</description></item><item><title>November 14, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/11/14/november-14-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/11/14/november-14-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team and Michael DeTorre from VMLY&amp;amp;R to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap and to present the Demo Content sample pages.
Recording Resources Slides - November 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.8.12</title><link>/blog/2023/11/14/virtual-y-1.8.12/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/11/14/virtual-y-1.8.12/</guid><description>Bug fixes only Resolved an issue with the Avocado welcome email resulting in a fatal error. (#1184) Fixed an issue with Log Exports failing under D10 (#904) Under VY 1.8.1 and Drupal 10.0.10 VY content didn’t load on the dashboard or on individual items. (#924) Top menu was overlapping the main menu for admin users. (#1103) Credit: Kairamkonda Rajesh Virtual Meeting/Live Stream Description was missing in D10. (#1166)</description></item><item><title>October 10, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/10/10/october-10-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/10/10/october-10-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Tom Gardner, Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap including features slated for the December 2023 release. Guest presenter and SEO expert Richard Nosek shared his knowledge about Google Analytics 4.
Recording Resources Slides - October 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.0</title><link>/blog/2023/09/12/digital-services-release-10.3.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/09/12/digital-services-release-10.3.0/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Expanding upon the June 2023 release, we are making the final set of page components and content types compatible with Layout Builder. We have also improved the design and functionality of some existing components and content types.
Learn more in our docs.
Home / Preferred Branch Camp Content Type Camp Menu (Microsite Menu) Camp Quick Links Facility Content Type Alerts VirtualY Small Banner Branch Amenities component redesign Icon Grid component redesign LB Events Allow Content Editors to customize Branch Contact info on Layout Builder Event node pages.</description></item><item><title>September 12, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/09/12/september-12-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/09/12/september-12-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Stasya Paliienko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to demonstrate newly released features from the September release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight features demonstrated by Stasya Paliienko and Avi Schwab include:
Layout Builder content types for Camp, Facility, Branch, and Event Content Overview documentation links Ability to compare Revisions of pages Updated CK Editor Support for adding Structured Schema data and Metadata Recording Resources Slides - September 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>August 8, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/08/08/august-8-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/08/08/august-8-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden and Shelley Goetz from the Core team and Dan Dieffenbach and Jessica Stroot from YMCA360 to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap, including a demonstration of the YMCA360 Web and mobile product.
Recording Resources Slides - August 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>July 11, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/07/11/july-11-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/07/11/july-11-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Stasya Paliienko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - July 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.2.14.1</title><link>/blog/2023/06/27/digital-services-release-10.2.14.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/27/digital-services-release-10.2.14.1/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Donations Updated Donation component to display in all 4 color schemes Fixed issue related to giving amount fields Fixed issue with component layout in tablet views Menus &amp;amp; Global Elements Search bar and logo were made editable Header and Footer can be added to new Layout Builder content types Fixed an issue with the hamburger menu displaying on large screens Added a placeholder for the Google Translate block in Layout Builder Fixed issue with Alerts related to the hamburger menu Ensured links of only 1 level display in the expanded mega menu (i.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.8.0</title><link>/blog/2023/06/19/virtual-y-1.8.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/19/virtual-y-1.8.0/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Made VirtualY compatible with Layout Builder and Drupal 10 Bug Fixes Resolved issues with Virtual Y Live Chat, and created documentation Added a fix to ensure that autologout doesn’t occur if a user is playing a video Fixed some minor bugs related to 1:1 meetings</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.2.14</title><link>/blog/2023/06/14/digital-services-release-10.2.14/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/14/digital-services-release-10.2.14/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder v3.1 Expanding upon the March 2023 release, we are making additional page components and content types compatible with Layout Builder. Learn more in our docs.
The final set of components and content types will be completed in the September 2023 release.
Global Header / Footer Elements All the components needed for a configurable header and footer, including logo, search, translate menu, main menu, footer, etc.</description></item><item><title>June 13, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/06/13/june-13-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/13/june-13-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, Stasya Paliienko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - June 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>May 9, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/05/09/may-9-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/05/09/may-9-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - May 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Activity Finder Security Notice</title><link>/blog/2023/04/18/activity-finder-security-notice/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/04/18/activity-finder-security-notice/</guid><description>Summary Activity Finder could provide an attack vector where a malicious site could use the “trusted” YMCA domain to redirect users to an untrusted site.
Sites using Activity Finder should immediately ensure they have activity_finder_trusted_redirect_host_patterns configured in settings.php as per the documentation and update to the latest release of Activity Finder.
What is the problem? Activity Finder provides a method for sites to redirect users to register for activities. The method passes a URL in a query string, like exampleymca.</description></item><item><title>April 11, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/04/11/april-11-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/04/11/april-11-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - April 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.6.6</title><link>/blog/2023/03/15/virtual-y-1.6.6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/15/virtual-y-1.6.6/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Updated documentation for VY 1:1 Meetings VY custom provider trims spaces from email addresses on CSV import. Bug Fixes Resolved issue with users not being able to join 1:1 Meetings Fixed broken previews for Shared Content. Applied a Gated Content patch to remove errors. Fixed menu styling issues. Resolved an issue with YouTube videos not displaying after JS is recompiled. Fixed VY Daxko SSO so that it does not intentionally overwrite the API whitelist URL.</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 9.2.13</title><link>/blog/2023/03/14/digital-services-release-9.2.13/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/14/digital-services-release-9.2.13/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder (v2) Expanding upon the December release, we are making additional components and content types compatible with Layout Builder. Learn more in our docs.
Modals
A pop-up / modal that can display on page load. Modal Documentation &amp;amp; Training Breadcrumbs
Secondary navigation that allows users to understand where they are located within a site. Breadcrumb Documentation &amp;amp; Training Testimonials component
Component for displaying short testimonials or quotes from Y members in an interactive carousel-style format.</description></item><item><title>March 14, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/03/14/march-14-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/14/march-14-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Shelley Goetz, Stasya Paliienko, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap. Stasya Paliienko demonstrates the Layout Builder version 2 components released today.
Recording Resources Slides - March 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>Layout Builder Roadmap</title><link>/blog/2023/03/09/layout-builder-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/09/layout-builder-roadmap/</guid><description>Skip to: v1 | v2 | v3
Layout Builder v1 Released in 9.2.12, December 2022
Page components Accordions Expandable pairs of question/answer or header/section fields. Maps to paragraphs: accordion_section, faq, ymca_accordion Cards (Horizontal &amp;amp; Vertical) Flexible cards style components. Carousels A full-width display with multiple sets of a header, description, and call to action overlaid on an image Grid CTA Content Sets of headline, description, and link displayed in n-item wide rows.</description></item><item><title>February 14, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/02/14/february-14-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/02/14/february-14-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team, as well as Steven Wright from Daxko to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap. Avi demonstrates comparing a page created with Paragraphs to an equivalent page created using the new Layout Builder, and Steven shares details about the new Daxko API.
Recording Resources Slides - February 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>January 10, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/01/10/january-10-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/01/10/january-10-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest information about:
Daxko and GXP Embedded Code updates 2023 site planning, including Migration to Drupal 10 Budgeting for end of year 2024 for migration off of paragraphs Layout builder V2 Training and Documentation Overview Incorporate of Events page feedback Welcome YMCA of Metro Atlanta to the community!</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.6.5</title><link>/blog/2022/12/16/virtual-y-1.6.5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2022/12/16/virtual-y-1.6.5/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features 9.4 Virtual Y Update Updated Virtual Y to version 9.4 Bug Fixes Virtual Y: In Event Series, Host&amp;rsquo;s Name is not editable The Host&amp;rsquo;s Name is now included as an editable field when updating an existing Event Series, or it should always copy the values from the editable Instructor field&amp;rsquo;s upon each Save. Virtual Y: Released bug fixes - April 2022 Removed additional styling below the menu Chat - Fixed an issue with Chat to remove message history/previous chat Fixed an issue with the page layout breaking for small videos Resolved error that was displaying when admin tried to install Virtual 1:1 Meeting module Fixed an issue with megamenu links going to the secondary menu Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to create an export file with logs Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to install Open Y Virtual YMCA Search module Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to install Open Y Virtual Y shared content server module Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to install Virtual Y Shared Content module Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to export Users logs Fixed an issue where the time of a 1:1 meeting doesn’t match on the Schedules and 1:1 meeting page Fixed an issue where users weren’t able to join the 1:1 meeting Fixed an issue where admins could not index searches Fixed a problem with the secondary menu shifting Resolved an issue in Lily where page titles were partially hidden on mobile devices VirtualY 1.</description></item><item><title>Website Services 9.2.12</title><link>/blog/2022/12/14/website-services-9.2.12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2022/12/14/website-services-9.2.12/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder (version 1) Content editors now have a new tool in their toolbelt for building dynamic landing pages - Layout Builder! The “Landing Page (Layout Builder)” content type enables editors to build custom landing pages with a new drag-and-drop interface. Learn more in our docs.
Accordion Components - Layout Builder v 1.0
Pairs of question / answer or header / body components that expand or collapse on-click to either hide or reveal content.</description></item><item><title>1 Column</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/1c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/1c/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for implements a paragraph with 1 column.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes Line Above field_prfg_display_line_above No Display a line above the column. Column field_prgf_1c_column No Enter column body. Paragraph Title field_prgf_1c_title No Enter title to display at the top of 1 column paragraph. Paragraph Description field_prgf_1c_description No Enter description to display under the 1 column paragraph title.</description></item><item><title>2 Columns</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/2c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/2c/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for implements a paragraph with 2 column.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes Line Above field_prfg_display_line_above No Display a line above the column. Left Column field_prgf_2c_left No Enter left column body. Right Column field_prgf_2c_right No Enter right column body.</description></item><item><title>3 Columns</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/3c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/3c/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for implements a paragraph with 3 column.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes Line Above field_prfg_display_line_above No Display a line above the column. Left Column field_prgf_3c_left No Enter left column body. Center Column field_prgf_3c_center No Enter center column body. Right Column field_prgf_3c_right No Enter right column body. Paragraph Title field_prgf_title No Enter title to display at the top of 3 columns paragraph.</description></item><item><title>4 Columns</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/4c/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/4c/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for implements a paragraph with 4 column.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes Line Above field_prfg_display_line_above No Display a line above the column. First Column field_prgf_4c_1st No Enter first column body. Second Column field_prgf_4c_2nd No Enter second column body. Third Column field_prgf_4c_3rd No Enter third column body. Fourth Column field_prgf_4c_4th No Enter forth column body. Button field_prgf_4c_button No Button with link to display under 4 column paragraph Paragraph Title field_prgf_title No Enter title to display at the top of 4 columns paragraph.</description></item><item><title>Activity</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/activity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/activity/</guid><description>Activity content type is used for adding Activities on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the activity item. Program Subcategory field_activity_category Yes A reference field for selecting the program subcategory. Content Area Field group Description field_activity_description No Textarea for the description/body with WYSIWYG, without summary. URL pattern Content type is using following pattern: /programs/[node:field_activity_category:entity:field_category_program:entity:title]/[node:field_activity_category:entity:title]/[node:title]</description></item><item><title>Alert</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/alert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/alert/</guid><description>Alert content type is used for adding alerts on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the activity item. Background color field_alert_color Yes Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Color&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Text color field_alert_text_color Yes Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Color&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Icon color field_alert_icon_color No Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Color&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Description for field: &amp;ldquo;Leave empty to hide icon.</description></item><item><title>All Amenities</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/all-amenities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/all-amenities/</guid><description>Provide a paragraph with a table view shows list of Branches.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description All amenities field_field_prgf_amnts_view No Predefined reference to a view to display all amenities. Title field_prgf_title No Enter title which is going to be displayed on top of the paragraph.</description></item><item><title>Amenities</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/amenities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/amenities/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding reference Branch amenities. We will use this for the Branch.
Machine_name: amenities</description></item><item><title>Area</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/area/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/area/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding location areas on the site. We will use this for the Location Branch and Facility CTs.
Machine_name: area</description></item><item><title>Article</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/article/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/article/</guid><description>Article content type is used for adding blog posts, news items, and press releases on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the article item. Sub-title default?? No Sub-title of the article item Locations field_article_location Yes Reference field to branch and camp nodes. Multiple Values. Category field_article_category No Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Blog Category&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Multiple Values. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites.</description></item><item><title>Banner</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/banner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/banner/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the banner content.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes Headline field_prgf_headline Yes Headline of the banner. Plain text, 255 characters Color field_prgf_color Yes Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Color&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Image field_prgf_image No Entityreference to media image. Single value. Description field_prgf_description No WYSIWYG field without summary. Link field_prgf_link No Link field that should store internal and external links.</description></item><item><title>Basic</title><link>/docs/content-structure/blocks/basic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/blocks/basic/</guid><description>A simple block with a description.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Content field_block_content Yes WYSIWYG field without summary.</description></item><item><title>Block Menu</title><link>/docs/content-structure/blocks/block-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/blocks/block-menu/</guid><description>Implements custom block type with a links.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Menu Links field_menu_block_links Yes The Menu Links. Color field_menu_block_color Yes Select colors for menu block background gradient. Text color field_menu_block_text_color Yes Select text color of the menu block.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/blog/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/blog/</guid><description>Blog Post content type is used for adding blog posts on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the blog item. Locations field_blog_location Yes Reference field to branch and camp nodes. Multiple Values. Category field_blog_category No Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Blog Category&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Multiple Values. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites.</description></item><item><title>Blog Category</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/blog-category/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/blog-category/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding blog categories on the site.
Machine_name: blog_category</description></item><item><title>Blog Posts Listing</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/blog-posts-listing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/blog-posts-listing/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest blog posts and utilizes exposed filters.
Location Category Text It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Bootstrap version support for Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/activity-finder/bootstrap-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/activity-finder/bootstrap-versions/</guid><description>In the Carnation theme we use bootstrap v 4.6 and for this case we have a special option Bootstrap version in settings form for Activity Finder v4 (/admin/openy/settings/activity-finder)
Rose and Lily themes are using Bootstrap v3, Carnation theme is on Bootstrap v4 And when we set it to 4 then the AF4 result page looks good for the tablet screen on Carnation</description></item><item><title>Branch</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/branch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/branch/</guid><description>Branch content type is used for adding Branches on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the branch item. Neighborhood field_location_area No A taxonomy reference field using the &amp;ldquo;Area&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Coming Soon field_location_state No A checkbox field to determine branches in development. Temporary URL field_location_temp_url No A link field to provide a temporary page URL (a blog post, or something else) if the branch is coming soon.</description></item><item><title>Branch Amenities</title><link>/docs/content-structure/blocks/branch-amenities/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/blocks/branch-amenities/</guid><description>A block with amenities list of the current branch.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Branch amenities field_branch_am Yes Uses only Custom Formatter to display a list of amenities within Paragraph block. Link field_sb_link No Link to display at the bottom of the block. Title field_sb_title No Title to display at top of block. Icon class field_icon_class No Provide a &amp;ldquo;Font Awesome&amp;rdquo; icon name, e.g. flag, car, info. Overrides image icon.</description></item><item><title>Branches Popup (All)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/branches-popup-all/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/branches-popup-all/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the locations selection popup, based on current node.
Relates to:
[Schedule search list](Schedule search list.md) [Classes Listing](Classes Listing.md) Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Branches Popup (Class)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/branches-popup-class/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/branches-popup-class/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the locations selection popup, based on current node.
Relates to:
[Class Sessions](Class Sessions.md) [Class Location](Class Location.md) Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Camp</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/camp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/camp/</guid><description>Camp content type is used for adding Camps on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the camp item. Menu links field_camp_menu_links Yes Link field with multiple values, that should have the Title and Link field. Based on it, we will complete the Camp Menu. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites.</description></item><item><title>Categories Listing</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/categories-listing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/categories-listing/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders all published categories according to current program page.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date(newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Class</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/class/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/class/</guid><description>Class content type is used for adding Classes on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the class item. Activity field_class_activity No A reference field for selecting the class. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites. Header Area Field group Content field_header_content No A paragraph embed field that will allow us to add various flexible content modules, from the predefined list of paragraph types.</description></item><item><title>Class Location</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/class-location/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/class-location/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the locations class location view mode, based on url query parameter location with a valid id.
Relates to [Branches Popup (Class)](Branches Popup (Class).md).
When the page has a location parameter the Branches Popup paragraph will make an &amp;ldquo;Edit&amp;rdquo; link on this paragraph visible. That link triggers the Branches Popup to open. Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block.</description></item><item><title>Class Sessions</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/class-sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/class-sessions/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the class session instances, based on url query parameter location with a valid id.
Relates to [Branches Popup (Class)](Branches Popup (Class).md).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display. Displayed table Location(should be displayed in case if &amp;amp;location=% not in the URL. Otherwise should be hiddedn. Time + date Registration(link) Details Online registration Ticket required In membership Age Min - Max Use cases Use case 3: Class page WITHOUT location popup 3.</description></item><item><title>Classes Listing</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/classes-listing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/classes-listing/</guid><description>Classes Listing - should display all published classes grouped by activity.
Classes Listing Filters - this paragraph should disply filter form for &amp;ldquo;Classes Listing&amp;rdquo; with following fields:
Location Program Sub-program Activity Relates to [Branches Popup (All)](Branches Popup (All).md).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display. Use cases Use case 1: Classes Listing paragraph on a Program subcategory page WITHOUT location popup paragraph 1.</description></item><item><title>Code</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/code/</guid><description>Provide paragraph containing a Code block. Can be used to embed Youtube video for instance.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Code field_prgf_code_block Yes Block reference to Code block. Create a new one or pick up an existed Code block.</description></item><item><title>Color</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/color/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/color/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding colors on the site.
Machine_name: color
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Name drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Color name. Color field_color Yes Color selector.</description></item><item><title>Custom Simple</title><link>/docs/content-structure/blocks/custom-simple/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/blocks/custom-simple/</guid><description>A simple block with a body.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Icon field_icon No Icon for block. Icon class field_icon_class No Provide a &amp;ldquo;Font Awesome&amp;rdquo; icon name, e.g. flag, car, info. Overrides image icon. Body field_sb_body No Enter body text. Link field_sb_link No Add link to the block. Title field_sb_title No Title to display at top of block.</description></item><item><title>Documentation Tips &amp; Tricks</title><link>/docs/contribution-guidelines/docs-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/contribution-guidelines/docs-tips/</guid><description>In addition to the full documentation, here are some commonly used functions in the YMCA Website Services Docs.
General Styles The YMCA Website Services Docs are written in Markdown, an easy-to read and write formatting language.
The old documentation made heavy use of horizontal rules --- and slashes in headings ## // Heading. We try to use standard Markdown headings for organization and remove those visual indicators for better accessibility.</description></item><item><title>Event</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/event/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/event/</guid><description>Event content type is used for adding events on the site.
Fields Label Machine Name Required Description Field Settings Notes Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the event item. Sub-title default?? No Sub-title of the event item. plain text Locations field_event_location Yes Reference field to branch and camp nodes. Multiple Values. Address for event; can be either a branch or non-branch location. Category field_event_category No Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Event Category&amp;rdquo; vocabulary.</description></item><item><title>Facility</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/facility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/facility/</guid><description>Facility content type is used for adding facilities on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the facility item. Neighborhood field_location_area No A taxonomy reference field using the Area Vocabulary(area). Type field_facility_type No A taxonomy reference field using the &amp;ldquo;Facility Type&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Facility Branch field_facility_loc No A entity reference field to reference the related Branch node. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites.</description></item><item><title>Facility Type</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/facility-type/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/facility-type/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding facility type on the site. We will use this for the Facility CT.
Machine name: facility_type</description></item><item><title>Featured Blog Posts</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-blog-posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-blog-posts/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the featured stories.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Headline field_prgf_headline No Headline of the banner. Blog Posts field_fblog_posts Yes Multiple values. Reference field to Blog posts.</description></item><item><title>Featured Content</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-content/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the featured content.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Headline field_prgf_headline No Headline of the featured content. Description field_prgf_description No Textarea for the description/body with WYSIWYG, without summary. Link field_prgf_link No Link field that supports internal and external URLs. Style field_prgf_grid_style Yes Select list with following values: 2:2 items per row, 3:3 items per row, 4:4 items per row Column description field_prgf_fc_clm_description No Multiple values.</description></item><item><title>Featured Highlights</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-highlights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-highlights/</guid><description>Provides a paragraph containing blocks of specific types positioned as 2, 3 or 4 blocks per row.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title field_prgf_title No Paragraph title. Style field_prgf_grid_style Yes Select list with following values: 2:2 items per row, 3:3 items per row, 4:4 items per row. Featured Highlights block field_prgf_block_ref_unlim Yes Create a new one or pick up an existing block of given types: Featured Highlight Block, Basic Block, Simple Block, Date block.</description></item><item><title>Featured News Posts</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-news-posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/featured-news-posts/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the featured news.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Headline field_prgf_headline No Headline of the banner. News Posts field_fnews_posts Yes Multiple values. Reference field to News posts.</description></item><item><title>Flexible</title><link>/docs/content-structure/blocks/flexible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/blocks/flexible/</guid><description>A block with amenities list of the current branch.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Node reference field_node_ref Yes Provide reference to Node.</description></item><item><title>Gallery</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/gallery/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the gallery content.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Headline field_prgf_headline Yes Headline of the gallery. Description field_prgf_description No WYSIWYG field without summary. Link field_prgf_link No Link field that should store internal and external links. Images field_prgf_images No Entityreference to media image. Multiple values.</description></item><item><title>Grid columns</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/grid-columns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/grid-columns/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for field_grid_columns the in Grid Content paragraph.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Description field_prgf_grid_clm_description No Textarea for the description/body with WYSIWYG, without summary. Headline field_prgf_clm_headline No Headline of the grid content. Icon field_prgf_clm_icon No Entityreference to media asset. Should allow to upload svgs. Icon class field_prgf_clm_class No Input field that allows to add the font-awesome icons needed. Description - &amp;ldquo;Provide a &amp;ldquo;Font Awesome&amp;rdquo; icon mane, e.</description></item><item><title>Grid Content</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/grid-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/grid-content/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the grid content stories.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Style field_prgf_grid_style Yes Select list with following values: 2:2 items per row, 3:3 items per row, 4:4 items per row Content field_grid_columns Paragraph Grid columns Description field_prgf_grid_clm_description No Textarea for the description/body with WYSIWYG, without summary. Headline field_prgf_clm_headline No Headline of the grid content. Icon field_prgf_clm_icon No Entityreference to media asset.</description></item><item><title>Group Schedules</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/group-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/group-schedules/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the group schedules from GroupEx Pro.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and is configurable in form display.</description></item><item><title>Landing Page</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/landing-page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/landing-page/</guid><description>Landing Page content type is used for adding landing pages on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the landing page item. Layout field_lp_layout Yes Select list with the options: one_column_clean|One Column - Full widthone_column|One Columntwo_column|Two Columnstwo_column_fixed|Two Columns with fixed sidebar (sticky at the top) Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites.</description></item><item><title>Landing Page (Layout Builder)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/lb-landing-page/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/lb-landing-page/</guid><description>Landing Page content type is used to add Landing Pages to your website using Layout Builder widgets.
This page is managed with Layout Builder. You may want to uncheck &amp;ldquo;Publish Content&amp;rdquo; before creating a page, use the &amp;ldquo;Layout&amp;rdquo; tab to build the content, then Publish when the page is complete. See our User Guide for help.
Fields Label Machine Name Required Description Field Settings Notes Title title yes Title of Landing Page Metadata Field group Meta description field_meta_description no Short text used for metatags and cards Text (plain, long) Meta image field_meta_image no Media image reference for use in metatags and cards Entity reference (Media image) Meta tags field_meta_tags no Provided by Metatag module URL pattern Content type is using following pattern: [node:title]</description></item><item><title>Latest Blog Posts</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-blog-posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-blog-posts/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest blog posts that are promoted to the front page.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Latest Blog Posts (Branch)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-blog-posts-branch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-blog-posts-branch/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest blog posts associated with a branch.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Latest Blog Posts (Camp)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-blog-posts-camp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-blog-posts-camp/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest blog posts associated with a camp.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Latest News Posts</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-news-posts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-news-posts/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest news posts that are promoted to the front page.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Latest News Posts (Branch)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-news-posts-branch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-news-posts-branch/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest news posts associated with a branch.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Latest News Posts (Camp)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-news-posts-camp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/latest-news-posts-camp/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest news posts associated with a camp.
It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Limited Time Offer</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/limited-time-offer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/limited-time-offer/</guid><description>This Paragraph add limited time offer for Home Page based on Landing Page CT.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Subtitle field_lto_subtitle No Enter subtitle for Limited time offer. Link field_lto_link No Add link for Latest time offer. Title field_lto_title No Enter title for the Limited Time Offer.</description></item><item><title>Linting</title><link>/docs/contribution-guidelines/linting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/contribution-guidelines/linting/</guid><description>lint•er : noun
a machine for removing the short fibers from cotton seeds after ginning a static code analysis tool used to flag programming errors, bugs, stylistic errors and suspicious constructs Checking for broken links Using linkcheck:
Linkcheck has some issues with localhost that we&amp;rsquo;re working on resolving. Until then, you can set up your local site to run through Cloudflare Tunnel and then run it.
linkcheck -e https://your-site-url.example.com/docs/some/path --skip-file .</description></item><item><title>Location finder</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/location-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/location-finder/</guid><description>This is paragraph that renders the Location finder block.
Location finder block contains locations views displays with branches, camps and facilities.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Location finder field_prgf_location_finder No Block reference to the location_finder block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Location finder filters</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/location-finder-filters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/location-finder-filters/</guid><description>This is paragraph that renders the Location finder map with pins and filters.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Location finder field_prgf_location_finder No Block reference to the location_finder block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display. Tags style field_prgf_lf_tags_style Yes Tags style that will be used for map tags filter. Default - checkboxes. Second option is multiselect widget with checkboxes.</description></item><item><title>Media Tags</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/media-tags/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/media-tags/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding media tags that will allow you to structure your media assets library.
Machine name: media_tags</description></item><item><title>Membership</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/membership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/membership/</guid><description>Membership content type is used for adding membership on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the membership item. Description field_mbrshp_description Yes Textarea for the description/body with WYSIWYG, without summary. Image field_mbrshp_image Yes Media field to upload the image. Membership info field_mbrshp_info Paragraph Paragraph to indicate the location where the membership is available and the URL. Location field_mbrshp_location No Select list with locations (branches).</description></item><item><title>Membership info</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/membership-info/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/membership-info/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for field_mbrshp_info the in Membership CT.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Location field_mbrshp_location No Select list with locations (branches). Single value. Link field_mbrshp_link No Link field to provide the membership redirect URL. Join Fee field_mbrshp_join_fee No Dollar value for how much someone has to pay to join. Monthly Rate field_mbrshp_monthly_rate No Dollar value for the monthly fee of the membership.</description></item><item><title>Microsites menu</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/microsites-menu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/microsites-menu/</guid><description>Provide paragraph containing a microsites menu block.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Menu Block field_prgf_block_ref Yes Block reference to the view/block. Create a new one or pick up an existed menu block. Hide Main Menu field_prgf_ms_menu_hide_menu No Whether to hide or not the main website menu.</description></item><item><title>News</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/news/</guid><description>News Post content type is used for adding news posts on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the news item. Locations field_news_location Yes Reference field to branch and camp nodes. Multiple Values. Category field_news_category No Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;News Category&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Multiple Values. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites.</description></item><item><title>News Category</title><link>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/news-category/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/taxonomy/news-category/</guid><description>This is a vocabulary that will be used for adding news categories on the site.
Machine_name: news_category</description></item><item><title>News Posts Listing</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/news-posts-listing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/news-posts-listing/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest news posts and utilizes exposed filters.
Location Category Text It uses sticky at the top option and order items based on published date (newest at the top).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Program</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/program/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/program/</guid><description>Program content type is used for adding Programs on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the program item. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites. Header Area Field group Icon field_program_icon No A image field, supporting .svg for uploading the program icon. Image field_program_image No A image field, for uploading the program image.</description></item><item><title>Program Registration (Daxko)</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/program-registration-daxko/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/program-registration-daxko/</guid><description>This is paragraph that renders the Programs Search Block.
Programs Search Block provides a form to search programs from Daxko.
Relates to: Daxko
Daxko &amp;amp; Program Registration (Daxko) configuration must be setup before the Program Registration paragraph will work.
Configuration setting at /admin/config/development/daxko/programs-search
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Program registration block field_prgf_reg_block No Block reference to the programs_search_block block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Program Subcategory</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/program-subcategory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/program-subcategory/</guid><description>Program Subcategory content type is used for adding program subcategories on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the program subcategory item. Program field_category_program Yes A reference field for selecting the program. Meta Tags field_meta_tags No A meta tags field allows us to provide structured metadata and Graph meta tags for Facebook, Pinterest, LinkedIn and other social networking sites. Header Area Field group Image field_category_image No A image field, for uploading the category image.</description></item><item><title>Promo Card</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/promo-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/promo-card/</guid><description>This is a Paragraph type that will be used for the Promo Cards.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title field_prgf_title No Title of the Promo Card. Headline field_prgf_headline Yes Headline of the Promo Card. Description field_prgf_description No WYSIWYG field without summary. Link field_prgf_link No Link field that should store internal and external links.</description></item><item><title>Promotion</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/promotion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/promotion/</guid><description>Promotions are timed pieces of content that allow content editors the flexibility to create a single item that can be placed in multiple locations on the site, without having to duplicate or manage content in multiple locations.
Fields Name Machine name Field type Required? Title title yes Subtitle field_subtitle Text (plain) CTA / link field_link Link no Description field_promo_description Text (formatted, long) no Image field_promo_media Entity reference yes Pages field_promo_visibility_pages Text (plain, long) Promotion Category field_promo_category Entity reference no Promotion Priority field_promo_priority List (text) yes Promotion visibility state field_promo_visibility_state List (text) yes URL pattern No URL pattern.</description></item><item><title>Schedule search form</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/schedule-search-form/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/schedule-search-form/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the session instances filters for [Schedule search list](Schedule search list.md).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display.</description></item><item><title>Schedule search list</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/schedule-search-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/schedule-search-list/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the session instances, based on url parameters, and or filters from [Schedule search form](Schedule search form.md).
Relates to [Branches Popup (All)](Branches Popup (All).md).
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Block field_prgf_block Yes Block reference to the view/block. Should have default value and should be hidden in form display. Use cases Use case 1: Schedule search list paragraph on a page WITHOUT location popup paragraph 1.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Secondary Description and Sidebar</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/secondary-description-and-sidebar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/secondary-description-and-sidebar/</guid><description>This is a Paragraph type that will be used for the paragraphs with left (secondary description) and right (sidebar) blocks.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Left Column field_prgf_left_column_block No Block reference to: Basic Block, Code Block, Date block or Simple Block. Create a new one or pick up an existed block. Right Column field_prgf_right_column_block No Block reference to: Basic Block, Code Block, Date block or Simple Block. Create a new one or pick up an existed block.</description></item><item><title>Session</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/session/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/session/</guid><description>Session content type is used for adding Sessions on the site.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the session item. Class field_session_class Yes A reference field for selecting the program subcategory. Session Info Field group - - Description field_session_description No Textarea for the description/body with WYSIWYG, without summary. Gender field_session_gender No Select List with Gender options: Coed, Male, Female. Online registration field_session_online No Boolean field that determines if the Register Now button/link gets displayed.</description></item><item><title>Session Time</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/session-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/session-time/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for field_session_time the in Session CT.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Date &amp;amp; Time field_session_time_date No This will use Drupal date/time fields &amp;amp; should be a single date field with &amp;rsquo;end date&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;end time&amp;rsquo; option enabled. Days field_session_time_days No Checkboxes with following values: Sunday, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday</description></item><item><title>Simple Content</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/simple-content/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/simple-content/</guid><description>Simple Content is used for adding text to the pages.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Content field_prgf_description Yes WYSIWYG field without summary.</description></item><item><title>Small Banner</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/small-banner/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/small-banner/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the banner content.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes Color field_prgf_color Yes Reference field for choosing the term from &amp;ldquo;Color&amp;rdquo; vocabulary. Headline field_prgf_headline Yes Headline of the Small banner. Plain text, 255 characters Image field_prgf_image No Entityreference to media image. Single value. Description field_prgf_description No WYSIWYG field without summary.</description></item><item><title>Social Post</title><link>/docs/content-structure/content-types/social-post/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/content-types/social-post/</guid><description>Social Post content type is used for adding Social Posts on the site. Social Posts are grabbed from social networks.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title drupal&amp;rsquo;s default Yes Title of the program item. ID field_id Yes Post Id in social network. This is system field. Is used by post fetcher. Image field_image No Image field for saving post image. Can save jpg and png formats. Link field_link no Contains link to original post in social network.</description></item><item><title>Social Post Listing</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/social-post-listing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/social-post-listing/</guid><description>This is dynamic paragraph that renders the latest social posts that were imported from social networks.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title field_prgrf_sl_title No Title for block with social posts. Description field_prgrf_sl_description No Description for block with social posts. Social List field_prgrf_sl_block No Reference to views block which select posts and show them as masorny grid.</description></item><item><title>Social Share Icons</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/social_share_icons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/social_share_icons/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the add social media share. See more How to configure AddThis
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Notes</description></item><item><title>Story Card</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/story-card/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/story-card/</guid><description>This is a Paragraph type that will be used for the Story Cards.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title field_prgf_title No Title of the Story Card. Headline field_prgf_headline Yes Headline of the Story Card. Link field_prgf_link No Link field that should store internal and external links.</description></item><item><title>Teaser</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/teaser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/teaser/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the teaser content.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Title field_prgf_title No Title of the Teaser. Image field_prgf_image No Entityreference to media image. Single value. Description field_prgf_description No WYSIWYG field without summary. Link field_prgf_link No Link field that should store internal and external links.</description></item><item><title>Webform</title><link>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/webform/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/paragraphs/webform/</guid><description>This is a paragraph type that will be used for the embedding webforms.
Fields Name Machine name Required Description Embedded Webform field_prgf_webform No Embedded webform entityreference (select). Single value. Default webform submission data (YAML) field_prgf_webform_default_data No YAML code for passing in default values to webform. Webform status field_prgf_webform_status No Status of webform on render. Radio with 2 options, open or closed (Closed prevents further submissions).</description></item><item><title>WYSIWYG View Modes</title><link>/docs/content-structure/media/wysiwyg-view-modes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/content-structure/media/wysiwyg-view-modes/</guid><description>Listed view modes are available for embedding in WYSIWYG editor.
View Modes Name Machine name Description Full embedded_full This view mode displays media asset with full width. Half embedded_half This view mode displays media asset with half width and uses alignment. Link embedded_link This view mode displays link to media asset. Bundles details Image In &amp;ldquo;Full&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Half&amp;rdquo; view modes image should be display in &amp;lt;img&amp;gt; tag with appropriate classes. Link - should lead to the original image with target=blank.</description></item></channel></rss>