<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Releases on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/blog/releases/</link><description>Recent content in Releases on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/blog/releases/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.3</title><link>/blog/2024/06/12/digital-services-release-10.3.3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/06/12/digital-services-release-10.3.3/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Drupal Updates Learn more about the improvements in Drupal 10.1 and Drupal 10.2.
For users who wish to apply all the updates below without Drupal 10.2, we&amp;rsquo;ve released YMCA Website Services 10.3.2.4. This can be applied as a stepping stone to Drupal 10.2, but we recommend moving to 10.2 as community security support for Drupal 10.0 ended in December 2023.
Updated to Drupal core version 10.2. (#758) NOTE: This release will work with Drupal 10.</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.2.1</title><link>/blog/2024/03/28/digital-services-release-10.3.2.1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/28/digital-services-release-10.3.2.1/</guid><description>Bug Fixes [Promotion Content Type] Admins can view a preview of promotion items before publishing. (#1333) [Layout Builder] Fixed the button fill of the CTA button in the Program Categories listing view block. (#1334) [Menus] Fixed issue with menu links with long text not wrapping on mobile devices. (#1337) [Layout Builder] Made dropdown icons in the Article/Events filters clickable. (#1352) Fixed broken Header in Lily theme. (#1353) [Layout Builder] Fixed stretched body field inside Layout Builder components.</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.2</title><link>/blog/2024/03/12/digital-services-release-10.3.2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/12/digital-services-release-10.3.2/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Updates Continuing general cleanup, updated documentation, and improvements to the content editing experience for new Layout Builder components and content types.
Learn more in our docs.
Layout Builder - Program CT - Added styling for &amp;ldquo;Categories listing&amp;rdquo; view block to match the new styles for headers, buttons, etc. (#1273) Layout Builder - Simple Content / WYSIWYG - Included approved brand headers colors into the default color selector.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.9.0</title><link>/blog/2024/03/12/virtual-y-1.9.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/12/virtual-y-1.9.0/</guid><description>Updates Upgraded Axios library for Virtual Y. (#889) Polyfill Security update. (#1357)</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.1.1</title><link>/blog/2023/12/12/digital-services-release-10.3.1.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/12/12/digital-services-release-10.3.1.1/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Promotion Content Type Promotions are pieces of content with scheduled start and end dates that can be used for displaying internal marketing and ad campaigns. Content editors can easily schedule, manage and place multiple promotions throughout their website via the Drupal admin interface.
The first version of this content type allows content editors to place promotions inside the Card component (for Layout Builder) and as interstitial content within Activity Finder.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.8.18</title><link>/blog/2023/12/12/virtual-y-1.8.18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/12/12/virtual-y-1.8.18/</guid><description>Bug Fixes Fixed an issue with YV Logs using the old instructor name field. (#903) Fixed the Header (utility menu and main nav) so that it does not overlap the content below. (#1076) Fixed the empty description on Live Stream/Virtual Meeting causing the page to fail. (#1240) Credit: Sathya Raja</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.0.1</title><link>/blog/2023/11/14/digital-services-release-10.3.0.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/11/14/digital-services-release-10.3.0.1/</guid><description>Sandbox Demo Content Pages Home page Who We Are (About) Programs Overview Programs Category (i.e. Youth Sports) Individual Program (i.e. Soccer) Membership Join Donate Location Finder Location page (i.e. YMCA Springfield) Schedules Events Individual Event Contact Us Jobs Volunteer Opportunities Documentation Updates Drupal 10 update assistance. (#787) Documentation for Layout Builder Facility Content Type. (#1034) Documentation for Layout Builder Icon Grid component. (#1041) Documentation for Alerts. (#1035) Added instructions for adding/restoring the Camp Header block state.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.8.12</title><link>/blog/2023/11/14/virtual-y-1.8.12/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/11/14/virtual-y-1.8.12/</guid><description>Bug fixes only Resolved an issue with the Avocado welcome email resulting in a fatal error. (#1184) Fixed an issue with Log Exports failing under D10 (#904) Under VY 1.8.1 and Drupal 10.0.10 VY content didn’t load on the dashboard or on individual items. (#924) Top menu was overlapping the main menu for admin users. (#1103) Credit: Kairamkonda Rajesh Virtual Meeting/Live Stream Description was missing in D10. (#1166)</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.3.0</title><link>/blog/2023/09/12/digital-services-release-10.3.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/09/12/digital-services-release-10.3.0/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Expanding upon the June 2023 release, we are making the final set of page components and content types compatible with Layout Builder. We have also improved the design and functionality of some existing components and content types.
Learn more in our docs.
Home / Preferred Branch Camp Content Type Camp Menu (Microsite Menu) Camp Quick Links Facility Content Type Alerts VirtualY Small Banner Branch Amenities component redesign Icon Grid component redesign LB Events Allow Content Editors to customize Branch Contact info on Layout Builder Event node pages.</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.2.14.1</title><link>/blog/2023/06/27/digital-services-release-10.2.14.1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/27/digital-services-release-10.2.14.1/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder Donations Updated Donation component to display in all 4 color schemes Fixed issue related to giving amount fields Fixed issue with component layout in tablet views Menus &amp;amp; Global Elements Search bar and logo were made editable Header and Footer can be added to new Layout Builder content types Fixed an issue with the hamburger menu displaying on large screens Added a placeholder for the Google Translate block in Layout Builder Fixed issue with Alerts related to the hamburger menu Ensured links of only 1 level display in the expanded mega menu (i.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.8.0</title><link>/blog/2023/06/19/virtual-y-1.8.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/19/virtual-y-1.8.0/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Made VirtualY compatible with Layout Builder and Drupal 10 Bug Fixes Resolved issues with Virtual Y Live Chat, and created documentation Added a fix to ensure that autologout doesn’t occur if a user is playing a video Fixed some minor bugs related to 1:1 meetings</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 10.2.14</title><link>/blog/2023/06/14/digital-services-release-10.2.14/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/14/digital-services-release-10.2.14/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder v3.1 Expanding upon the March 2023 release, we are making additional page components and content types compatible with Layout Builder. Learn more in our docs.
The final set of components and content types will be completed in the September 2023 release.
Global Header / Footer Elements All the components needed for a configurable header and footer, including logo, search, translate menu, main menu, footer, etc.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.6.6</title><link>/blog/2023/03/15/virtual-y-1.6.6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/15/virtual-y-1.6.6/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Updated documentation for VY 1:1 Meetings VY custom provider trims spaces from email addresses on CSV import. Bug Fixes Resolved issue with users not being able to join 1:1 Meetings Fixed broken previews for Shared Content. Applied a Gated Content patch to remove errors. Fixed menu styling issues. Resolved an issue with YouTube videos not displaying after JS is recompiled. Fixed VY Daxko SSO so that it does not intentionally overwrite the API whitelist URL.</description></item><item><title>Digital Services Release 9.2.13</title><link>/blog/2023/03/14/digital-services-release-9.2.13/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/14/digital-services-release-9.2.13/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder (v2) Expanding upon the December release, we are making additional components and content types compatible with Layout Builder. Learn more in our docs.
Modals
A pop-up / modal that can display on page load. Modal Documentation &amp;amp; Training Breadcrumbs
Secondary navigation that allows users to understand where they are located within a site. Breadcrumb Documentation &amp;amp; Training Testimonials component
Component for displaying short testimonials or quotes from Y members in an interactive carousel-style format.</description></item><item><title>Virtual Y 1.6.5</title><link>/blog/2022/12/16/virtual-y-1.6.5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2022/12/16/virtual-y-1.6.5/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features 9.4 Virtual Y Update Updated Virtual Y to version 9.4 Bug Fixes Virtual Y: In Event Series, Host&amp;rsquo;s Name is not editable The Host&amp;rsquo;s Name is now included as an editable field when updating an existing Event Series, or it should always copy the values from the editable Instructor field&amp;rsquo;s upon each Save. Virtual Y: Released bug fixes - April 2022 Removed additional styling below the menu Chat - Fixed an issue with Chat to remove message history/previous chat Fixed an issue with the page layout breaking for small videos Resolved error that was displaying when admin tried to install Virtual 1:1 Meeting module Fixed an issue with megamenu links going to the secondary menu Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to create an export file with logs Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to install Open Y Virtual YMCA Search module Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to install Open Y Virtual Y shared content server module Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to install Virtual Y Shared Content module Resolved an error that was displaying when admin tried to export Users logs Fixed an issue where the time of a 1:1 meeting doesn’t match on the Schedules and 1:1 meeting page Fixed an issue where users weren’t able to join the 1:1 meeting Fixed an issue where admins could not index searches Fixed a problem with the secondary menu shifting Resolved an issue in Lily where page titles were partially hidden on mobile devices VirtualY 1.</description></item><item><title>Website Services 9.2.12</title><link>/blog/2022/12/14/website-services-9.2.12/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2022/12/14/website-services-9.2.12/</guid><description>Updates &amp;amp; New Features Layout Builder (version 1) Content editors now have a new tool in their toolbelt for building dynamic landing pages - Layout Builder! The “Landing Page (Layout Builder)” content type enables editors to build custom landing pages with a new drag-and-drop interface. Learn more in our docs.
Accordion Components - Layout Builder v 1.0
Pairs of question / answer or header / body components that expand or collapse on-click to either hide or reveal content.</description></item></channel></rss>