<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Decoupled Applications on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/tags/decoupled-applications/</link><description>Recent content in Decoupled Applications on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/decoupled-applications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/activity-finder/</guid><description>YCloudYUSA/yusaopeny_activity_finder is bundled as a &amp;ldquo;decoupled application&amp;rdquo; that ships with the YMCA Website Services distribution.
Requirements This module requires the following modules:
openy_map (For pulling the list of location-related content types.) This module also requires one of the following to store data:
A Solr server (preferably a server or index per-environment). A subscription with access to the Daxko API. Recommended modules Activity Finder is most often used with a syncer to pull data from an external source.</description></item><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/activity-finder/</guid><description>Activity Finder combines data from the Activity, Class, and Session content types into an interactive tool that can be used with Paragraphs or Layout Builder pages.
Out-of-the-box, YMCA Website Services’s Activity Finder integrates with Daxko, ActiveNet, and Personify. Configuring these integrations is mostly user-friendly, but often is supported by a partner development team. Any other CRM will require custom developer work.
See the Program Event Framework developer docs for a full list of integrations.</description></item><item><title>Group Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</guid><description>Sometimes called &amp;ldquo;Group Exercise&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Group Schedules&amp;rdquo;, the Repeat Schedules block provides a similar view to Activity Finder, but focuses on recurring, often drop-in classes. You can see an example of this on our sandbox site.
Developers can find more information in ynorth-project/openy_repeat and Program Event Framework.
As of August 2024, the Schedules have an updated design with improved functionality and user experience. The improved design will also respond to the selected colorway and page styles.</description></item><item><title>Membership Calculator</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/membership/calculator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/membership/calculator/</guid><description>The Membership Calculator is bundled with the distribution in the openy_calc module.
As of August 2024, the Membership Calculator has an updated design with improved functionality and user experience. The improved design will also respond to the selected colorway and page styles.
Configuring the Calculator The Membership Calculator uses Membership content items. Those will need to be created in order for the Membership Calculator to function.
First, create a Membership node for each membership type your Branch or Association offers.</description></item><item><title>Membership Framework</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/membership/framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/membership/framework/</guid><description>The Membership Framework is distributed in the openy_memberships repository and must be added and installed on top of the base distribution. We recommend working with your development partner if you wish to go this route.
Check out the Membership Framework sandboxes for a demonstration.
Membership Landing Pages To get started with the Membership Framework you will first need to create a number of landing pages.
The examples below use Paragraphs, but similar pages can be created using Layout Builder blocks and the Membership Framework custom block.</description></item><item><title>PEF Schedules</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/pef-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/pef-schedules/</guid><description>YCloudYUSA/y_pef_schedule
The Y PEF Schedule module provides a calendar functionality for scheduling events. It includes a Vue.js component, fullcalendar-app, to display and interact with the calendar.
Requirements Drupal Open Y Repeat Vue.js 3 Axios-HTTP FullCalendar Installation composer require ycloudyusa/y_pef_schedule drush en y_pef_schedule lb_simple_schedule Install as you would normally install a contributed Drupal module. For further information, see Installing Drupal Modules. Enable the module by navigating to Admin &amp;gt; Extend (/admin/modules) in your Drupal admin interface, then enabling &amp;ldquo;Y PEF Schedules Admin tool&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;LB Simple Schedule&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Simple Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/simple-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/simple-schedules/</guid><description>YCloudYUSA/y_pef_schedule
See PEF Schedules for installation instructions.
Once you install the PEF Schedules module, you will be able to build schedules and add sessions via a calendar-based builder.
Before you start Create schedule groupings The Schedule editor allows Content Editors to create Sessions on a &amp;ldquo;WYSIWYG&amp;rdquo; calendar interface. As described in the PEF data model, Sessions require Classes, which require Activities, which require Program Subcategories, which require Programs.
flowchart LR subgraph &amp;#34;PEF Relationships&amp;#34; direction LR Session -- requires --&amp;gt; Class Class -- references --&amp;gt; Activity Activity -- references --&amp;gt; PS PS -- requires --&amp;gt; Program PS[&amp;#34;Program Subcategory&amp;#34;] end You will need to create at least a Class and Activity to start adding events to the calendar.</description></item></channel></rss>