<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Decoupled Applications on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/tags/decoupled-applications/</link><description>Recent content in Decoupled Applications on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/decoupled-applications/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/activity-finder/</guid><description>Activity Finder combines data from the Activity, Class, and Session content types into an interactive tool that can be used with Paragraphs or Layout Builder pages.
Out-of-the-box, YMCA Website Services’s Activity Finder integrates with Daxko, ActiveNet, and Personify. Configuring these integrations is mostly user-friendly, but often is supported by a partner development team. Any other CRM will require custom developer work.
See the Program Event Framework developer docs for a full list of integrations.</description></item><item><title>Group Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</guid><description>Sometimes called &amp;ldquo;Group Exercise&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Group Schedules&amp;rdquo;, the Repeat Schedules block provides a similar view to Activity Finder, but focused more on recurring, often drop-in classes. You can see an example of this on our sandbox site.
Developers can find more information in ynorth-project/openy_repeat and Program Event Framework.
Using Group Schedules Repeat Schedules Paragraph Using Repeat Schedules in Layout Builder is not yet supported.</description></item><item><title>Membership Calculator</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/membership/calculator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/membership/calculator/</guid><description>The Membership Calculator is bundled with the distribution in the openy_calc module.
Configuring the Calculator The Membership Calculator uses Membership content items. Those will need to be created in order for the Membership Calculator to function.
First, create a Membership node for each membership type your Branch or Association offers. Then, inside each Membership node, add a Membership Info Paragraph with the details of that membership at each of your Locations.</description></item><item><title>Membership Framework</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/membership/framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/membership/framework/</guid><description>The Membership Framework is distributed in the openy_memberships repository and must be added and installed on top of the base distribution. We recommend working with your development partner if you wish to go this route.
Check out the Membership Framework sandboxes for a demonstration.
Membership Landing Pages To get started with the Membership Framework you will first need to create a number of landing pages.
The examples below use Paragraphs, but similar pages can be created using Layout Builder blocks and the Membership Framework custom block.</description></item><item><title>PEF Schedules</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/pef-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/pef-schedules/</guid><description>YCloudYUSA/y_pef_schedule
The Y PEF Schedule module provides a calendar functionality for scheduling events. It includes a Vue.js component, fullcalendar-app, to display and interact with the calendar.
Installation Download and install the module in your Drupal project. Enable the module by navigating to Admin &amp;gt; Extend in your Drupal admin interface. Go to the /admin/openy/branch-schedules and select a branch. Usage After choosing a brunch, you can view the calendar, the main features of the calendar:</description></item><item><title>Simple Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/simple-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/simple-schedules/</guid><description>YCloudYUSA/y_pef_schedule
See PEF Schedules for installation instructions.
User instructions are coming soon.</description></item></channel></rss>