<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Activity Finder on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/tags/activity-finder/</link><description>Recent content in Activity Finder on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/activity-finder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/activity-finder/</guid><description>YCloudYUSA/yusaopeny_activity_finder is bundled as a &amp;ldquo;decoupled application&amp;rdquo; that ships with the YMCA Website Services distribution.
Requirements This module requires the following modules:
openy_map (For pulling the list of location-related content types.) This module also requires one of the following to store data:
A Solr server (preferably a server or index per-environment). A subscription with access to the Daxko API. Recommended modules Activity Finder is most often used with a syncer to pull data from an external source.</description></item><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/layout-builder/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/layout-builder/activity-finder/</guid><description>Activity Finder combines data from the Activity, Class, and Session content types into an interactive tool. Learn more about Activity Finder.
To use the block:
Click the Layout tab at the top of your page Scroll to the location on the page where you want to add a block Click Add block In the sidebar, click Create custom block Choose the block to add. Configure the options:
See Activity Finder Block Configuration for field details.</description></item><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/activity-finder/</guid><description>A screenshot showing the Activity Finder block and a detail popup. See a live example of Activity Finder in our sandbox site.
How it Works This paragraph type requires an integration into a CRM. See Program Activity Framework for a list of existing integrations. Any other CRM will require custom developer work.
How you use these paragraphs will depend on how your Association has structured its program data on the CRM and on how you decide to get people to program results.</description></item><item><title>Activity Finder</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/activity-finder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/activity-finder/</guid><description>Activity Finder combines data from the Activity, Class, and Session content types into an interactive tool that can be used with Paragraphs or Layout Builder pages.
Out-of-the-box, YMCA Website Services’s Activity Finder integrates with Daxko, ActiveNet, and Personify. Configuring these integrations is mostly user-friendly, but often is supported by a partner development team. Any other CRM will require custom developer work.
See the Program Event Framework developer docs for a full list of integrations.</description></item><item><title>Activity, Class, and Session</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/content-types/activity-class-session/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/content-types/activity-class-session/</guid><description>Content editors rarely, if ever, enter information directly into these content types on a day-to-day basis. However, it is important to know how they work and how they relate to manually-entered content.
Example - Swim Lessons
Swimming and Aquatics (Program Page, manually entered) Swim Lessons (Program Subcategory Page, manually entered) Youth Group Swim Lessons (Activity, mapped from CRM or custom automation) Stage 3 (Class, mapped from CRM) Monday/Wednesday/Friday 9:30-10 a.m. at Franklin Family YMCA (Session, mapped from CRM) Note: This is an example only.</description></item><item><title>Program Event Framework</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Program Event Framework&amp;rdquo; refers to the entire ecosystem of content and modules in YMCA Website Services that work together to build Activity Finder, Group Schedules, and more.
Content Types These provide the containers for PEF content in Drupal:
Program Program Subcategory Activity, Class, Session Syncers These provide integrations to pull content from external systems into the content types:
Extended Daxko API Integration (drupal/openy_daxko2) Simple Daxko Integration (deprecated) (drupal/daxko) ActiveNet Integration (drupal/activenet) Personify Integration (drupal/personify) GroupEx Pro (Daxko) Integration (drupal/groupexpro) PEF (Program Event Framework) GXP (GroupEx Pro) Sync (ynorth-projects/openy_pef_gxp_sync) YMCA 360 (Y360) Integration (drupal/yusaopeny_ymca360) Traction Rec Integration (ycloudyusa/openy_traction_rec) How to configure the Traction Rec integration How to import data from Traction Rec Displays These display the content for users to discover:</description></item></channel></rss>