<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Group Schedules on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/tags/group-schedules/</link><description>Recent content in Group Schedules on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/group-schedules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Group Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</guid><description>Sometimes called &amp;ldquo;Group Exercise&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Group Schedules&amp;rdquo;, the Repeat Schedules block provides a similar view to Activity Finder, but focuses on recurring, often drop-in classes. You can see an example of this on our sandbox site.
Developers can find more information in ynorth-project/openy_repeat and Program Event Framework.
As of August 2024, the Schedules have an updated design with improved functionality and user experience. The improved design will also respond to the selected colorway and page styles.</description></item><item><title>Program Event Framework</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Program Event Framework&amp;rdquo; refers to the entire ecosystem of content and modules in YMCA Website Services that work together to build Activity Finder, Group Schedules, and more.
Content Types These provide the containers for PEF content in Drupal:
Program Program Subcategory Activity, Class, Session Syncers These provide integrations to pull content from external systems into the content types:
Extended Daxko API Integration (drupal/openy_daxko2) Simple Daxko Integration (deprecated) (drupal/daxko) ActiveNet Integration (drupal/activenet) Personify Integration (drupal/personify) GroupEx Pro (Daxko) Integration (drupal/groupexpro) PEF (Program Event Framework) GXP (GroupEx Pro) Sync (ynorth-projects/openy_pef_gxp_sync) YMCA 360 (Y360) Integration (drupal/yusaopeny_ymca360) Traction Rec Integration (ycloudyusa/openy_traction_rec) How to configure the Traction Rec integration How to import data from Traction Rec Displays These display the content for users to discover:</description></item><item><title>Repeat Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/layout-builder/repeat-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/layout-builder/repeat-schedules/</guid><description>Repeat Schedules combines data from the Activity, Class, and Session content types into an interactive tool. Learn more about Group Schedules.
Before you can use the Repeat Schedules block, you will need to:
Ensure the openy_repeat module is updated to at least 2.2.0. Enable the Repeat (Group) Schedules (lb_repeat_schedules) module at Admin &amp;gt; Extend (/admin/modules). To use the block:
Click the Layout tab at the top of your page Scroll to the location on the page where you want to add a block Click Add block In the sidebar, click Create custom block Choose the block to add.</description></item><item><title>Repeat Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/repeat-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/repeat-schedules/</guid><description>Sometimes called “Group Exercise” or “Group Schedules”, the Repeat Schedules block provides a similar view to Activity Finder, but focused more on recurring, often drop-in classes.
See Group Schedules for more details.
Examples On the sandbox site.
How to use To use the Repeat Schedules paragraph:
Expand the Content Area on a Landing Page. Choose Add Repeat Schedules. See Group Schedules Block Configuration for configuration details. Save the page. What fields are where See Group Schedules Front-end.</description></item></channel></rss>