<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Group Schedules on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/tags/group-schedules/</link><description>Recent content in Group Schedules on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/group-schedules/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Group Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/schedules/group-schedules/</guid><description>Sometimes called &amp;ldquo;Group Exercise&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Group Schedules&amp;rdquo;, the Repeat Schedules block provides a similar view to Activity Finder, but focused more on recurring, often drop-in classes. You can see an example of this on our sandbox site.
Developers can find more information in ynorth-project/openy_repeat and Program Event Framework.
Using Group Schedules Repeat Schedules Paragraph Using Repeat Schedules in Layout Builder is not yet supported.</description></item><item><title>Program Event Framework</title><link>/docs/development/program-event-framework/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/program-event-framework/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Program Event Framework&amp;rdquo; refers to the entire ecosystem of content and modules in YMCA Website Services that work together to build Activity Finder, Group Schedules, and more.
Content Types These provide the containers for PEF content in Drupal:
Program Program Subcategory Activity, Class, Session Syncers These provide integrations to pull content from external systems into the content types:
Extended Daxko API Integration (drupal/openy_daxko2) Simple Daxko Integration (deprecated) (drupal/daxko) ActiveNet Integration (drupal/activenet) Personify Integration (drupal/personify) GroupEx Pro (Daxko) Integration (drupal/groupexpro) PEF (Program Event Framework) GXP (GroupEx Pro) Sync (ynorth-projects/openy_pef_gxp_sync) YMCA 360 (Y360) Integration (drupal/yusaopeny_ymca360) Traction Rec Integration (ycloudyusa/openy_traction_rec) How to configure the Traction Rec integration How to import data from Traction Rec Displays These display the content for users to discover:</description></item><item><title>Repeat Schedules</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/repeat-schedules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/repeat-schedules/</guid><description>Examples On the sandbox site.
How to use To use the Repeat Schedules paragraph:
Expand the Content Area on a Landing Page. Choose Add Repeat Schedules. Configure the options: PDF Schedule link - a link to a manually-generated PDF as an alternative to the automatically generated one. Clear All link - where the user is directed when they use the &amp;ldquo;Clear all&amp;rdquo; link. Limit by category - choose categories aith autocomplete to only show certain categories.</description></item></channel></rss>