<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Monthly Calls on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/blog/monthly-calls/</link><description>Recent content in Monthly Calls on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/blog/monthly-calls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>August 13, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/08/13/august-13-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/08/13/august-13-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Shelley Goetz and Avi Schwab from the Core team and Michael DeTorre, Joe Michaelson, and Jeff Greer from VMLY&amp;amp;R to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s coming up in the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Services roadmap.
Agenda items include:
Release Schedule Reminder An explanation of the Small Y Template project Font Licensing - for Cachet and Montserrat fonts Product Roadmap Reminder Community Call Time Change - Now on the 2nd Wednesday of each month at 11am CT Virtual Y - Sunset Reminder Recording Resources Slides - August 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>July 9, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/07/09/july-9-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/07/09/july-9-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Shelley Goetz and Avi Schwab from the Core team to discuss what&amp;rsquo;s coming up in the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Services roadmap.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release Schedule Changes Description of the Small Y Template Security Updates Virtual Y - sunsetting at end of 2024 Recording Resources Slides - July 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>June 11, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/06/11/june-11-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/06/11/june-11-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Stasya Paliienko, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to demonstrate features in the June release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release timeline updates Showcasing new Activity Finder updates Layout Builder improvements: Scheduling Options, Updated Schema, and Meta Tags Canadian Colorway Improvements Virtual Y - sunsetting at end of 2024 Recording Resources Slides - June 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>May 7, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/05/07/may-7-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/05/07/may-7-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Avi Schwab and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to demonstrate features in the forthcoming June release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release timeline updates Showcasing new Activity Finder updates A closer look at Website Service&amp;rsquo;s Next Generation Design System The &amp;ldquo;dark mode&amp;rdquo; enhancements and why they are important. Recording Resources Slides - May 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>April 8, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/04/08/april-8-2024/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/04/08/april-8-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, and Roman Salo from the Core team to demonstrate newly released features from the March point release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Release timeline updates Demo of updates to Weekly Schedule Management An in-depth description of the website update process from YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Cloud Hosting Service and YMCA partners Recording Resources Slides - April 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>March 12, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/03/12/march-12-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/03/12/march-12-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Roman Salo, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to demonstrate newly released features from the March release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight agenda items include:
Demo of Weekly Schedule Management Explanation of the Polyfill issue fix Description of the Text Editor fix for creating buttons Events entry and display improvements, now with recurring options! Traction Rec Integration Update Recording Resources Slides - March 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>February 9, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/02/09/february-9-2024/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/02/09/february-9-2024/</guid><description>Sandeep Goswami and Tom Gardner are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap, including an update about the TractionRec/Y-CRM, upcoming security updates, and addressing community questions.
Recording Resources Slides - February 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>January 9, 2024</title><link>/blog/2024/01/09/january-9-2024/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2024/01/09/january-9-2024/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap.
Recording Due to a technical issue there is no meeting recording available.
Resources Slides - January 2024 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>December 12, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/12/12/december-12-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/12/12/december-12-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap, including a demonstration the new Promotion content type and the Program &amp;amp; Subprogram content types in Layout Builder.
Recording Resources Slides - December 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>November 14, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/11/14/november-14-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/11/14/november-14-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Avi Schwab, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team and Michael DeTorre from VMLY&amp;amp;R to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap and to present the Demo Content sample pages.
Recording Resources Slides - November 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>October 10, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/10/10/october-10-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/10/10/october-10-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Tom Gardner, Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, and Shelley Goetz from the Core team to review the current state of the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap including features slated for the December 2023 release. Guest presenter and SEO expert Richard Nosek shared his knowledge about Google Analytics 4.
Recording Resources Slides - October 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>September 12, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/09/12/september-12-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/09/12/september-12-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Stasya Paliienko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to demonstrate newly released features from the September release of YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service.
Highlight features demonstrated by Stasya Paliienko and Avi Schwab include:
Layout Builder content types for Camp, Facility, Branch, and Event Content Overview documentation links Ability to compare Revisions of pages Updated CK Editor Support for adding Structured Schema data and Metadata Recording Resources Slides - September 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>August 8, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/08/08/august-8-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/08/08/august-8-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden and Shelley Goetz from the Core team and Dan Dieffenbach and Jessica Stroot from YMCA360 to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Services roadmap, including a demonstration of the YMCA360 Web and mobile product.
Recording Resources Slides - August 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>July 11, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/07/11/july-11-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/07/11/july-11-2023/</guid><description>Tom Scarborough is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Stasya Paliienko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - July 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>June 13, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/06/13/june-13-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/06/13/june-13-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner is joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, Stasya Paliienko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - June 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>May 9, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/05/09/may-9-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/05/09/may-9-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - May 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>April 11, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/04/11/april-11-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/04/11/april-11-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap.
Recording Resources Slides - April 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>March 14, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/03/14/march-14-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/03/14/march-14-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Shelley Goetz, Stasya Paliienko, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap. Stasya Paliienko demonstrates the Layout Builder version 2 components released today.
Recording Resources Slides - March 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>February 14, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/02/14/february-14-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/02/14/february-14-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team, as well as Steven Wright from Daxko to share the latest news about the YMCA&amp;rsquo;s Website Service roadmap. Avi demonstrates comparing a page created with Paragraphs to an equivalent page created using the new Layout Builder, and Steven shares details about the new Daxko API.
Recording Resources Slides - February 2023 YUSA Community Call</description></item><item><title>January 10, 2023</title><link>/blog/2023/01/10/january-10-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/blog/2023/01/10/january-10-2023/</guid><description>Tom Gardner and Tom Scarborough are joined by Kylie Aldridge-Ogden, Shelley Goetz, Andrii Podanenko, and Avi Schwab from the Core team to share the latest information about:
Daxko and GXP Embedded Code updates 2023 site planning, including Migration to Drupal 10 Budgeting for end of year 2024 for migration off of paragraphs Layout builder V2 Training and Documentation Overview Incorporate of Events page feedback Welcome YMCA of Metro Atlanta to the community!</description></item></channel></rss>