<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Membership Calculator on YMCA Website Services</title><link>/tags/membership-calculator/</link><description>Recent content in Membership Calculator on YMCA Website Services</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/tags/membership-calculator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Membership Calculator</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/membership/calculator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/membership/calculator/</guid><description>The Membership Calculator is bundled with the distribution in the openy_calc module.
Configuring the Calculator The Membership Calculator uses Membership content items. Those will need to be created in order for the Membership Calculator to function.
First, create a Membership node for each membership type your Branch or Association offers. Then, inside each Membership node, add a Membership Info Paragraph with the details of that membership at each of your Locations.</description></item><item><title>Membership Calculator Paragraph</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/membership-calculator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/paragraphs/membership-calculator/</guid><description>See Membership Calculator and Membership Content Type for more information.
Areas it Should Be Used Content Area Bottom Area How to Use Membership Calculator From the paragraphs drop-down, add the Membership Calculator. No additional configuration is necessary on the page.</description></item><item><title>Membership Content Type</title><link>/docs/user-documentation/content-types/membership/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/user-documentation/content-types/membership/</guid><description>See Membership Calculator.
Membership Fields General Information Title: The title of the membership type to be displayed on the first step of the Membership Calculator. Description: A short description to be displayed on the first step of the Membership Calculator. Image: A reusable image field to be displayed on the first step of the Membership Calculator. Membership Info The Membership Info Paragraph lists detailed membership information per location. Add one &amp;ldquo;Membership Info&amp;rdquo; section for each location that your membership applies to.</description></item></channel></rss>